我真的需要……
I really need to...
持有它。
Hold it.
不要看!
Don't look!
我爱你。
I love you.
你不必回答我。
You don't have to say it back.
我很抱歉。我只是…
I'm sorry. I just...
我爱你。
I love you.
♪我一直在操模特
♪ I been fuckin' models
♪我整晚都在弹瓶子
♪ I been poppin' bottles all night
♪洞里的花花公子
♪ playboy in the grotto
♪把它放在你的脸上，男孩♪
♪ put it on your face, boy ♪
他们不那么虚无主义
Sophie: They're not as nihilistic
当他们在互联网上搜索时
as they look on the Internet.
他们只是想让你这么想。
That's just, like, what they want you to think.
大卫以为你是他的青梅竹马。
So, David thinks you're a childhood friend.
嗯。是啊，他其实是
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, he actually was, um,
我幼儿园的男朋友。
my preschool boyfriend.
当然，在我意识到我是一个愤怒的拉拉之前。
Of course, before I realized that I was a raging dyke.
哇。
Wow.
他们看起来都很令人印象深刻。
They all look so impressive.
你让人印象深刻。
You're impressive.
是的,当然。
Yeah, sure.
我是认真的。
I'm serious.
乔丹会迷上你的。
Jordan is going to be obsessed with you.
所以…
So...
♪我觉得爸爸就是个混蛋
♪ I feel daddy as fuck
♪在一辆粉色的卡车里，爸爸就是他妈的
♪ whippin' in a pink truck, daddy as fuck
♪他想要进入我的肠子
♪ he wanna get in my guts
♬舔我的阴蒂，直到我疯了，爸爸他妈的
♪ lickin' my clit 'til I nut, daddy as fuck...
那是谁?
Who is that?
我的妈妈。
My mom.
♪哦，爸爸是他妈的我感觉爸爸是他妈的
♪ Ooh, daddy as fuck I feel daddy as fuck
你这个小怪物。
You little freak.
我…我不是。我只是…
I'm... I'm not. I just...
她会没事的，好吗?
She's gonna be fine, all right?
紧张是正常的。
It's okay to be nervous.
这就是乐趣所在。
That's part of the fun.
♪爸爸就像我妈的感觉，我觉得
♪ Daddy as fuck I feel, I feel...
♪哦，爸爸是他妈的我感觉爸爸是他妈的
♪ Ooh, daddy as fuck I feel daddy as fuck
♪爸爸像他妈的我觉得爸爸像他妈的
♪ daddy as fuck I feel daddy as fuck
♪我觉得，我觉得，我觉得
♪ I feel, I feel, I feel
来操我吧，我好饥渴，哈哈!♪我> < /
♪ Come fuck me, I'm horny, haha! ♪
这该死的窗户。
Ugh, this fucking window.
一定会很有趣的!
It's gonna be so fun!
你要来吗?
You coming?
是的。嗯…
Yeah. Um...
我把东西忘在车里了。
I forgot something in the car.
好吧……
Okay...
不要花太长时间。
Don't take too long.
你的游戏。
Your game.
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my god!
苏菲:令人惊讶的是,婊子!
Sophie: Surprise, bitches!
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my god!
你他妈的婊子!
You fucking whore!
大卫:搞什么鬼?这是索菲娅。
David: What the fuck? It's Sophie.
苏菲:婊子!哦……
Sophie: Bitch! Oh...
她在这里做什么?
What is she doing here?
我不知道。艾丽斯:哦,哦……
I don't know. Alice: Oh, oh...
你好!
Hello!
苏菲:你把我弄湿了，你这个坏女孩。
Sophie: You got me soaking wet, you bad little girl.
艾丽斯:来这里……格雷格:哇,男孩!
Alice: Come here... Greg: Whoo, boy!
嘿，我赢了吗?
Hey, did I win?
是的,格雷格。
Yes, Greg.
我告诉过你们。我的肺真的很大!
I told you guys. I got really big lungs!
大卫:我知道。
David: I know.
爱丽丝:哦，天哪。
Alice: Oh, my god.
真不敢相信你来了
I can't believe you're here, like,
上次见到你的时候
last time I saw you,
你在地铁上嗑嗨了，
you were coked out on the subway,
像只小鬣狗一样在地板上撒尿。
pissing on the floor like a little hyena.
我以为你是纽约大学的学生。
I thought you were an nyu student.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
这就是为什么我们不能再让母鸡怪物出来了。
And that is why we do not let the henny monster out anymore.
不,不!
No, no!
好吧，说真的，你怎么样?
Okay, but, seriously, how are you?
我很好。是的。是吗?
I'm good. Yeah. Yeah?
是啊，我真的很厉害。很好。好。
Yeah, i'm, like, really good. Good. Good.
你看起来很好。
You look so good.
我想念你!我也想你。
I miss you! I miss you too.
还有，我不得不说，我喜欢播客。
Also, I have to say, love the podcast.
好吧，我们有个吊舱的粉丝。
Okay, we have a fan of the pod.
我们喜欢播客。
We love the podcast.
爱丽丝:豆荚的粉丝。
Alice: A fan of the pod.
哦,我的上帝!见到你真是太好了!
Oh, my god! It's so good to see you!
真不敢相信你来了!这是,什么?
I can't believe that you're here! It's, like, what?
你好。嗨,我是艾玛。嗨。
Hi. Hi, I'm Emma. Hi.
哦,我的上帝。我很抱歉。
Oh, my god. I'm so sorry.
我太没礼貌了。我是爱丽丝。
That was so rude of me. I'm Alice.
伙计们，这是蜜蜂。
You guys, this is bee.
碧，这是大家。
Bee, this is everyone.
那是大卫，我最好的朋友
That's David, my best friend
在整个，整个，整个广阔的世界里。
in the whole, whole, whole wide world.
这是艾玛。
That's Emma.
这是乔丹,…
That's Jordan, and...
“吃晚饭!我是格雷格。
'Sup! I'm Greg.
“吃晚饭,球员!我是索菲娅。
'Sup, player! I'm Sophie.
哦!
Oh!
哇。你是苏菲吗?
Whoa. You're Sophie?
你能来真是太好了，苏苏。
Real nice of you to make it, soph.
辣，辣，乔丹。
Ooh, spicy, spicy, Jordan.
这是什么意思?
What is that supposed to mean?
乔丹:只是说我们都来过
Jordan: Just means that we have all been here
没人知道你会来。
and nobody had any fucking clue that you were coming.
更不用说一小时前了
Let alone, an hour before
暴风雨就要来了，所以…
the storm is supposed to start, so...
什么?我跟你们说过了
What? I totally told you guys
我来了。
that I was coming.
我给你发短信了。
And I texted you.
在群聊里?是的。
In the group chat? Yeah.
不,你没有。无论如何,
No, you didn't. Whatever,
你们知道我不擅长发短信吧?
you guys know that i'm useless with text, right?
还有，我们本来打算昨天来的，
Also, we meant to come up yesterday,
但后来bee被安排去上班了，所以…
but then bee got scheduled for a shift at work, so...
哦，你在哪里工作?
Oh, where do you work?
Gamehut。埃玛:噢,好。
Gamehut. Emma: Oh, nice.
爱丽丝:你们怎么这么奇怪?
Alice: Why are you guys being so weird?
你是在说我吗?
Are you talking about me?
你拿着香槟干什么?艾丽斯:伙计们!
What are you doing with that champagne? Alice: Guys!
你知道你不能碰我爸的东西。
You know you're not supposed to touch my dad's shit.
索菲娅在这里。好吧,这是索菲娅。
Sophie is here. Okay, it's Sophie.
这是千载难逢的景象。
It's a once in a millennium sighting.
我们正在做它。大卫:不。
We're doing it. David: No.
是的,来吧。
Yes, come on.
谁想打开它?格雷格:我来吧。
Who wants to pop it? Greg: I'll do it.
格雷格，你能帮我打开它吗?是啊，我会把它戳破的。
Greg, you'll help me pop it? Yeah, I'll pop it.
好的。是的。
Okay. Yeah.
蜜蜂:我,嗯…
Bee: I, um...
我带了一些东西。
I brought something.
哦!什么,嗯…它是什么?
Oh! What, uh... what is it?
这是,呃,西葫芦。一个面包。
It's, uh, zucchini. A bread.
这是西葫芦面包。大卫:谢谢你。
It's zucchini bread. David: Thank you.
百胜。
Yum.
嘿,书呆子。埃玛:这是甜的。
Hey, nerds. Emma: That's sweet.
哦,我的上帝!哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my, god! Oh, my god!
你是怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
你看到了吗?好吧。
Did you see that? All right.
没那么酷。这是疯狂的。
It's not that cool. That was crazy.
爱丽丝:哦，天哪!
Alice: Oh, my god!
艾玛:哇。哇。
Emma: Wow. Wow.
这太变态了。真不敢相信我们居然没录下来。
That was so sick. I can't believe we didn't video that.
把我爸爸的廓尔喀剑给我。
Give me my dad's Gurkha sword.
给我。在这里,男人。
Gimme that. Here, man.
操，太棒了。我刚在墙上找到的。
Fuck, that was so good. I just found it on the wall.
别从我墙上拿东西。
Yeah, don't grab shit off my wall.
哇!倒酒的时候小心点
Whoa! Eh, careful with that pour,
拉屎昂贵。
the shits expensive.
好吧，好吧。好了。好了。
All right, all right. There we go. There we go.
谢谢。真的让人印象深刻。
Thanks. Really impressive.
大卫:好浇注。
David: Nice pouring.
大学二年级生,你想要什么?我是清醒的。
Soph, you want? I'm sober.
耶!不,谢谢。
Yay! No, thanks.
恭喜。
Congrats.
格雷格:干杯。艾玛:干杯。
Greg: Cheers. Emma: Cheers.
格雷格:飓风!
Greg: To hurricanes!
乔丹:去飓风派对!
Jordan: To hurricane parties!
格雷格:是的。乔丹:飓风。
Greg: Yeah. Jordan: To hurricanes.
飓风。
To hurricanes.
乔丹:深。
Jordan: Deep.
这是开始的家伙!
Guys it's starting!
派对时间!
Party time!
开始。
Starting.
大便。他妈的。
Shit. Fuck.
好吧，麦克斯怎么了?
Okay, what's going on with Max?
没什么。他在哪里?
Nothing. Where is he?
他只是在休息。他会回来的。
He's just taking a break. He'll be back.
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
你就这点本事吗，混蛋!
Is that all you got, motherfucker!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
嘿,fuckface !
Hey, fuckface!
我们能谈谈吗?
Can we talk for a second?
你可以敲门吗?不，这是我的房子。
Can you knock? No, it's my house.
当然。有什么事吗?
Sure. What's up?
在私人。哦!
In private. Oh!
确定。
Sure.
我很抱歉。他会学习。
I'm sorry. He'll learn.
我马上回来。
I'll be right back.
大卫:是啊，汤姆·汉克斯在漂流者>里就是这么说的
David: Yeah, that's what Tom Hanks said in castaway.
她其实很可爱
She's actually really cute.
就像校园枪击案那样。
In like a school shooter type of way.
“给你带了西葫芦面包，戴夫。”
"Brought you zucchini bread, Dave."
她是我的。手了。
She's mine. Hands off.
乔丹:嘿。
Jordan: Hey.
噢,嗨……我…
Oh, hi... I...
呃，我只是…不不，我知道。
Uh, I was just... No, no, I know.
它是美丽的。这所房子。
It's beautiful. The house.
苏菲的父母有一个更大的。
Sophie's parents have one that's even bigger.
小心点，好吗?
Just be careful, okay?
索菲娅。只是…
With Sophie. Just...
小心些而已。
Be careful.
好的。
Okay.
但他，好像，一点都不性感。你明白我的意思吗?
But he's, like, not hot. You know what I mean?
他就像你妈妈一样
He's like, like, your mom
会说，“哦，他很性感。”
would be like, "ooh, he's hot."
不是你妈妈，我是说所有的妈妈。
Not your mom, I mean moms in general.
已经结婚的妈妈
Moms that have been married
10到15年之后，他们发现，
for like 10, 15 years and they see, like,
他从星巴克出来…
him going out of a Starbucks...
爱丽丝可以瞒着别人带个人来。
Alice got to bring someone without telling anyone.
所以你读了聊天。
So you do read the chat.
为什么大家都这么沉迷聊天?
Why is everyone so obsessed with the chat?
现在,你在这里。我在这里，我们在一起，对吧?
Now, you're here. I'm here, we're here together, right?
我们为什么要担心聊天的事?
Why are we worrying about the chat?
当我们能活在当下。
When we can just live in the moment.
是啊，因为你去了戒毒所
Yeah, it's 'cause you went to rehab
你也没有吸毒。
and you're not on drugs.
所以，一切就像，
So, like, everything is like,
"我们干嘛不都冷静点呢，伙计"
"ooh, why don't we just all be cool, man?"
你对格雷格有意见吗?
You have a little problem with Greg?
伐木工人。
The lumberjack.
这是一个新的豆荚。
It's a new pod.
我还不习惯吸入。
I'm not used to the inhaling yet.
他多大了，40岁吗?
What is he, like, 40?
我不知道。我想爱丽丝找到他了
I don't know. I think Alice found him
在陌陌上，或者别的什么。
on tinder, or some shit.
显然，他在阿富汗。
Apparently, he was in Afghanistan.
我想他在军队里，或者什么地方，所以…
I think he was in the army, or some shit, so...
这是热的。
Well, that's hot.
他不是……他没那么性感。
He's not... He's not, like, that hot.
你不必觉得他很有魅力，
You don't have to think he's attractive,
只要爱丽丝觉得他有吸引力就行了。
only Alice has to think that he's attractive.
就像，我觉得，
Like, I feel, like,
我比这更有吸引力。
I'm more attractive than that.
你会怎么做?绝对的。
You do? Absolutely.
它的特点是什么
And what are the features
你要拿出来谈吗?
that you're bringing to the table?
我看起来就像在做爱。
Well, I just look like I fuck.
你明白我的意思吗?嗯。
You know what I mean? Mmm.
我看起来像…我操。
I look like I... I fuck.
这就是我喜欢营造的氛围。
And that's the vibe I like to put out there.
是的。不,嗯,是的,
Yeah. No, uh, yeah,
他，他真的很帅。无论什么。
he's, he's really handsome. Whatever.
我是说，我们没必要一直谈论它。
I mean, we don't have to talk about it all the time.
你的脸怎么了?
What the fuck happened to your face?
他妈的马克斯。
Fucking Max.
马克斯,吗?是的，该死的麦克斯，真的。
Max did that? Yes, fucking Max, really.
好吧?我站在外面
Okay? I was standing outside
然后他就跑过来打我的眼睛。
and he just ran up to me and punched me in the eye.
刚跑到你面前?他只是这样做了。
Just ran up to you? He just did.
看它。他就这么走到你面前做了那件事，对吧?
Look at it. He just came up to you and did that, huh?
我认为它……实际上我认为它看起来
I think it... Actually think it looks
不过还是挺酷的。你不觉得吗?
kind of dope, though. Don't you think?
天越来越黑了。
It's getting fucking darker.
我看起来像个战士。对吧?
I look like a, like a warrior. Right?
就像，这有点…这很酷。
Like, it's kind of... It's kind of cool.
有点热。
Like, it's kind of hot.
比如，如果你看到我从7- 11便利店出来，
Like, if you saw me coming out of a 7-Eleven,
你就像…
you'd be like...
嗯…
Um...
那你有机会。
So have you had a chance to, uh,
跟我父母谈过吗?
talk to my parents at all?
你他妈在这干什么，苏苏?
What the fuck are you doing here, soph?
我错过了你。
I missed you.
我们都知道那是个谎言。
We both know that's a lie.
没有人想过我。
Nobody's ever missed me.
啊,不!请,不!
Ugh, no! Please, no!
天啊，你能把那个关了吗?
Ugh, my god, can you turn that off?
它让我心烦意乱。
It's bumming me out.
是的。你是对的。你是对的。
Yeah. You're right. You're right.
嘿，伙计们，我能…我能用上Wi-Fi吗?
Hey, guys, can I... Can I get on the Wi-Fi?
天啊，我总是记不住密码。
Oh, god, I can never remember the password.
这是一个很好的密码。
It's, like, an actually good password.
乔丹:我把它转过去。你的电子邮件是什么?
Jordan: I'll transfer it. What's your email?
蜜蜂:嗯…什么?
Bee: Uh... what?
你的电子邮件是什么?
What is your email?
嘿…
Hey...
我很抱歉。我的服务中断了，
I'm sorry. My service went out,
但我现在用的是Wi-Fi。
but I am on a Wi-Fi now.
所以,这很好。
So, that's good.
格雷格:我百分百想做抖音。你们都能做到。
Greg: I 100% wanna do a tiktok. All of you can do it.
好的。你知道这个吗?是哪一个?
Okay. Do you know this? Which one is it?
格雷格:我不知道我在做什么。
Greg: I don't know what I'm doing.
艾丽斯:遵循…我们会看…
Alice: Follow... We'll watch it...
你会赶上的。是的。
You'll catch it. Yeah.
好，准备，三，二…
Okay, ready, three, two...
埃玛:跟上，跟上。
Emma: Keep up, keep up.
乔丹:走吧!埃玛:看看你。
Jordan: Go! Emma: Look at you.
我们说到最后一部分了吗?
Are we at the last part?
乔丹:很好。这是好的。好的。
Jordan: That was good. That was good. Okay.
格雷格有点不听话，但我们正在检查他的动作。
Greg went a little rogue but we're checking the moves.
爱丽丝:不，你没有。再一次,再一次,再一次。
Alice: No, you didn't. Again, again, again.
埃玛:最后是这样。
Emma: At the end you go like this.
艾丽斯:准备好了吗?做好准备。你没事吧?
Alice: Ready? Get ready. You okay?
乔丹:我们应该把它贴出来。
Jordan: We should just, just post it.
爱丽丝:非常好。
Alice: It's very good.
乔丹:我准备好了。一次!
Jordan: I'm ready for the flow. One more time!
三，二，一，开始!
Three, two, one, go!
你想喝点什么吗?
Do you want a drink?
你想要点什么吗?
Do you want something?
给你。我们走吧!
Here you go. There we go!
她玩得很开心。
She's having a good time.
我们走吧!
Let's go!
是啊!哦,我的上帝。
Yeah! Oh, my god.
好吧,婊子。
Okay, bitch.
爱丽丝:我做得很咸。
Alice: I make it very salty.
这是令人难以置信的咸。
It's incredibly salty.
埃玛:这是你的初恋吗?
Emma: Is this your first relationship?
哦,不。
Uh, no.
你就是，给人那种感觉。
You just, kind of, give that vibe.
还不错。蜜蜂:是的。
Not in a bad way. Bee: Yeah.
你们在一起多久了?
How long have you guys been together?
哦，六周了。
Oh, uh, six weeks.
很好。哇。
Nice. Wow.
和苏菲共度六周。
Six weeks with Sophie.
爱丽丝。从好的方面来说，这很好。
Alice. In a good way, that's good.
你是莫斯科人吗?
Are you from Moscow?
蜜蜂:没有。哦。
Bee: No. Oh.
蜜蜂:为什么?
Bee: Why?
《日瓦戈医生》是我最喜欢的电影。
Doctor Zhivago is my favorite film.
我的天啊，
Alice: Ugh, my god,
这场风暴是怎么回事?
what is going on with this storm?
我要你做个决定。
I'm, like, make up your mind.
我想让它重新开始倾泻
I want it to start, like, pouring again
好让我们尽情疯狂。
so that we can go fucking crazy.
你知道里面有大麻吧?
Oh, you know that has weed in it, right?
没什么，我只是想让你知道。
Not a lot, I just wanted to let you know.
只是不想让你去镇上然后…
Just didn't want you to go to town and then...
艾玛:是的。你知道我的意思吗?
Emma: Yeah. Alice: You know what I mean?
哦，我们得到了很多赞。
Ooh, we're getting a lot of likes.
♪我很聪明
All: ♪ I'm smart
♪我强大的
♪ I'm strong
♪我已经准备好迎接任何事情的到来!
♪ I'm ready for whatever comes along!
♪我有好朋友
♪ I've got good friends
♪我们会坚持到最后
♪ we'll stick together to the end
♪嘿，我可以是答案
♪ Hey, I can be the answer
♪我准备好跳舞了，当吸血鬼升起
♪ I'm ready to dance when the vamp up
♪当我坠入深渊的时候拿起你的相机
♪ and when I hit that dip get your camera
♬你可以看到我是那个婊子自从娇惯
♪ you could see I been that bitch since the pamper
♪那我就是那小妹，那信标
♪ and that I am that young sis, the beacon
♪想要竞争的婊子
♪ the bitch who wants to compete and
♪我可以用peep和来装那个泵
♪ I can freak a fit that pump with the peep and
♬你知道你的婊子变成什么当她编织
♪ you know what your bitch become when her weave in
♪我只想抿一口那杯潘趣酒
♪ I just wanna sip that punch
噢!噢!他妈的什么?
ow! Ow! What the fuck?
♬踢你的婊子谁来自巴黎
♪ Kick it with your bitch who come from parisian
♬她知道我从哪里得到我的，和季节
♪ she know where I get mine from, and the season
大卫!噢!他妈的什么?
David! Ow! What the fuck?
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my god!
♬我猜那个女人被吃掉了
♪ I guess that cunt gettin' eaten
你是乱伦吗?
are you being an incel?
我磕了药，还咬了她。
I'm coked up and I bit her.
♪我在上城区的212路a
♪ I was in the 212 on the uptown a
♬黑鬼，你知道发生了什么事吗?
♪ nigga, you know what's up or don't you?
♪告诉你是谁造了你，我是个粗鲁的婊子，黑鬼
♪ Word to who made ya I'm a rude bitch, nigga
♪你是由什么组成的?
♪ what are you made up of?
♪我是一个把你的食物吃光的人，boo
♪ I'm a eat your food up, boo
♪我是一个看着对的人，黑鬼打赌你想做爱
♪ I'm a look right, nigga bet you do want to fuck
♪黑鬼更好，哦-跑-跑
♪ niggas better, ohh-run-run
♪你可能会被枪击，老乡
♪ you could get shot, homie
♪如果你真的想把你的枪举起
♪ if you do want to put your guns up
♪告诉你的船员不要前面我是个流氓，黑鬼
♪ tell your crew don't front I'm a hoodlum, nigga
原谅我。
excuse me.
♬婊子，我快要爆炸了
♪ Bitch, I'm 'bout to blew up too
♬我就是今天的那个人，我是新的狗屎boo
♪ I'm the one today I'm the new shit boo
那你有没有…
so did you, um...
你是在美国上的大学吗，还是…
Did you go to college here in the states, or, um...
是的,在这里……我是说，在犹他州。
Yeah, here... I, I mean, in Utah state.
你需要冷静一下。
Sophie: You need to chill out.
大卫:我猜。
David: I guess.
不，我是认真的，你得…
No, I'm serious, you need to...
你需要冷静下来。
You need to chill out.
我只是出汗了，我需要补充水分。
I'm just really sweaty and I need to hydrate myself.
好吗?
Okay?
你应该看好你的女朋友。
You should watch your girl.
看来她和乔丹玩得很开心。
Looks like she's having fun with Jordan.
♪当我出现的时候你要做什么?
♪ What you gon' do when I appear?
♪我何时首映?
♪ When I premiere?
♪婊子，你生命的尽头就在眼前
♪ Bitch, the end of your lives are near
♬这都是我的，我的!
♪ this shit been mine, mine!
♪婊子，我在212
♪ Bitch, I'm in the 212
♬第五个公鸡黑鬼它是第21动物园
♪ with the fifth cocked nigga it's the 21 zoo
♬当你的暴徒喷涌而出，你他妈的要做什么?
♪ fuck you gon' do when your goon sprayed up?
♬我打赌他的婊子不会得到他打赌你不会做什么
♪ Bet his bitch won't get him betcha you won't do much
♬看到即使你想要破灭
♪ see even if you do want to bust
♬你的婊子会让你削减和触摸你的船员也
♪ your bitch'll get you cut and touch your crew up too
♪pop，你在玩你的黄油
♪ pop, you playin' with your butter
♬像你的boo不会真的扣枪太
♪ like your boo won't true cock the gun too
♪你在哪里吃poom, hun
♪ where you do eat poom, hun
♪我在操你的小可爱q
♪ I'm fuckin' with your cutie q
♬你的鸡巴是什么样的，老乡，你喜欢什么?
♪ what's your dick like, homie what are you into?
♬你在跑什么，伙计?你在哪里醒来?
♪ What's the run dude? Where do you wake up?
告诉你的婊子继续恨…♪我> < /
♪ Tell your bitch keep hatin'... ♪
安静!
Silence!
乔丹:什么?停!
Jordan: What? Stop!
谁想玩肉体肉体肉体?
Who wants to play bodies bodies bodies?
大卫:啊,操!艾玛:是的!
David: Ah, fuck! Emma: Yes!
苏菲:所以，如果你画这张纸
Sophie: So, if you draw the piece of paper
上面有个"x"
that has the "x" on it,
你就是凶手。
you are the murderer.
你得保守这个秘密。
And you have to keep it a secret.
伙计们，每次玩这个我都很紧张。
Guys, I get so stressed out every time we play this.
总有人会以哭结束。
Someone always ends up crying.
爱丽丝:你最后总是哭。
Alice: You always end up crying.
好吧，我可以很容易地感知自己的情绪。
Okay, I can access my emotions easily.
非常容易。
Alice: Very incredibly easily.
她是个演员，她总是先哭。
She's an actress, she always cries first.
我只是说，这个游戏会变得很丑陋。
I'm just saying, this game gets very ugly.
我的天，才不是呢。
Oh, my god, no, it does not.
她一哭就很难看。
It gets ugly when she ugly cries.
艾玛:真的，每次我们玩的时候，
Emma: Literally, every single time we play,
人们开始战斗。
people start fighting.
大卫:是啊，这就是乐趣所在，艾玛。
David: Yeah, well, that's what makes it fun, Emma.
马克斯在哪儿?
Where's Max?
他不回我短信。
He's not responding to my texts.
哦,耶稣…
Oh, Jesus...
那么，你是怎么玩的?
So, how do you play?
苏菲:我马上要关灯了。
Sophie: So, I'm gonna hit the lights in a second.
如果你是凶手
And if you are the murderer,
你得偷偷摸摸地去杀人
you have to sneak around and kill someone
比如摸他们的后背。
by, like, touching them on the back.
然后，其他所有人都要避免被杀死。
And then, everyone else has to avoid being killed.
然后，如果你被杀了
And then, if you are killed,
你得倒下去假装自己死了。
you have to fall down and pretend you're dead.
艾丽斯:是这样的。
Alice: Like this.
格雷格:酷。
Greg: Cool.
嘿,嗯…爱丽丝，你想不想…
Hey, uh... Alice, do you wanna...
什么?大卫:你想不想……
What? David: Do you wanna...
你知道的。哦!对不起，我得走了。
You know. Oh! Excuse me, I have to go.
这是一个紧急情况。
It's an emergency.
原谅我。
Excuse me.
乔丹:最重要的部分
Jordan: The most important part
如果你发现了一具尸体
is if you do come across a body,
你得喊"尸体，尸体，尸体"
you have to yell, "bodies, bodies, bodies."
一旦发生这种情况，
And then, once that happens,
我们把灯都打开
we'll turn all the lights back on
然后我们会试着找出是谁干的。
and then we'll try to figure out who did it.
你能拿一下这个吗?
Could you hold this?
格雷格碰过那个吗?
Did Greg touch that?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
你对格雷格的态度太混蛋了。
You're being such a dick about Greg.
,就拿着这个。
Just hold this.
大卫……
David...
什么?我,呃……
What? I, ugh...
好吧……
Okay...
听着，到底怎么回事?
Look, what the fuck's going on?
苏菲:到地板上来。
Sophie: Come to the floor.
到地板上来。
Come to the floor.
乔丹:给我滚过来，小子。
Jordan: Get your ass over here, boy.
索菲:好的。好吧。
Sophie: Okay. All right.
乔丹:谁来主持呢?
Jordan: Who will do the honors?
哦……
Oh...
进入它。我们走吧。
Get into it. Let's go.
乔丹:噢!
Jordan: Ow!
啊!
Ahhh!
婊子。
Bitch.
爱丽丝:你生我气了吗?
Alice: Are you mad at me?
乔丹:没有。艾丽斯:好吧。
Jordan: No. Alice: Okay.
蜜蜂:噢!艾丽斯:乔丹!
Bee: Ow! Alice: Jordan!
苏菲:哇。什么?这是游戏。
Sophie: Whoa. What? It's the game.
大卫:Wowza……
David: Wowza...
哦,我的上帝…哦,来吧!
Oh, my god... Oh, come on!
那是什么?蜜蜂!
What was that? Bee!
你必须多击球。你得把
You have to hit more. You got to put
加点肌肉进去。你必须…是的，去吧。
some muscle into it. You gotta... Yeah, go for it.
是的。
Yeah.
来吧!
Come on!
乔丹:打他，他活该。
Jordan: Slap him around, he deserves it.
大卫:打我!
David: Fucking hit me!
埃玛:他想要。乔丹:不，他活该。
Emma: He wants it. Jordan: No, he deserves it.
这是他应得的。这样做。
He really deserves it. Do it.
如果有人该挨打，也应该是他。
If anyone deserves to be hit, it should be him.
是的。蜜蜂:好的。
Yeah. Bee: Okay.
看在上帝的份上。
Oh, for fuck sake like this.
爱丽丝:哦，天哪!
Alice: Oh, my god!
乔丹:大卫!大卫。
Jordan: David! David.
看到了吗?大卫。
See? David.
你这个混蛋!
You're a fucking dick!
什么?
What?
你真是个混蛋。
You are such an asshole.
我在教她怎么玩这个游戏。
I'm teaching her how to play the game.
宝贝，停，停!
Alice: Baby, stop, stop!
等等，伙计们，总得有人打我。
Wait, guys, someone has to hit me.
谁会打我?
Who's gonna hit me?
乔丹:我来吧。
Jordan: I'll do it.
埃玛:噢!
Emma: Ow!
谢谢你！乔丹:你是受欢迎的。
Thank you. Jordan: You're welcome.
索菲:好的!
Sophie: Okay!
我们准备好出发了吗?是的，我们他妈的走吧。
Are we ready to go? Alice: Yes, let's fucking go.
大卫:是的。爱丽丝:我们来玩游戏吧。
David: Yes. Alice: Let's play the game.
大卫:天啊!我太操蛋了。
David: Holy shit! I'm so fucked up.
啊。
Ahh.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
是的。
Yes.
蜜蜂:嘿。
Bee: Hey.
哦!
Oh!
苏菲:我看到白人……
Sophie: I see white man...
尸体,尸体,尸体!
Bodies, bodies, bodies!
你们!在这里。
You guys! Over here.
不!
No!
乔丹:好吧，谁想占我便宜
Jordan: All right, who tried to take advantage
我的身体在黑暗中?
of my body in the dark?
你的愿望,宝贝。
Your wish, babe.
爱丽丝:哦，为什么，天哪?为什么?他太性感了!
Alice: Oh, why, god? Why? He was so hot!
是你吗?不。
Was it you? No.
好的。那么，我们有提名吗?
Okay. So, do we have any nominations?
大卫:艾玛哇。
David: Emma whoa.
哇，快来了。什么?
Wow, coming in hot. What?
为什么?是的，我想是艾玛。
Why? Yup, I think it was Emma.
你为什么觉得是我?
Why do you think it was me?
是的，大卫，怎么了?
Alice: Yeah, David, why?
好吧，她就像，
David: Okay, well, she just, like,
赞同所有人所说的一切。
agrees with everything that everybody is saying.
这就是她在这个游戏中的策略
And that's her strategy in this game
而且每次都很有效。
and it works every single time.
我现在调用它。艾玛。
So, I'm just calling it now. It's Emma.
我们还有其他提名吗?
Sophie: Do we have any other nominations?
嗯…是的,大卫。
Um... yeah, David.
大卫:哦，得了吧。这是唾手可得的果实。
David: Oh, come on. It's low hanging fruit.
我是说，他是第一个扔石头的人。
I mean, he who casts the first stone.
比:伙计们，他为什么不动?
Bee: Guys, why isn't he moving?
格雷格?宝贝,起床了。
Greg? Baby, get up.
你没必要假装这么久。
You don't have to keep pretending for this long.
宝贝?来吧,格雷格。
Baby? Come on, Greg.
艾丽斯:格雷格……
Alice: Greg...
格雷格……
Greg...
起床了。
Get up.
等待。
Wait.
格雷格?
Greg?
格雷格!
Greg!
格雷格,起来!
Greg, get up!
格雷格!他不起来了。
Greg! He's not getting up.
放松点，这招总是管用的。我知道。
Hey, relax, this always works. I know.
哦,嘿!哦,我的上帝。
Oh, hey! Oh, my god.
你真的吓到我了。
You really scared me with that.
埃玛:格雷格，你真是个小骗子。
Emma: You're a little trickster, Greg.
乔丹:我知道，上帝啊。
Jordan: I know, Jesus Christ.
苏菲:可爱。
Sophie: Cute.
好吧,所以…大卫呢?
Okay, so... what about David?
艾丽斯:
Alice:
等等，也许是乔丹。
Wait, maybe it's Jordan.
当她是凶手时，她总是很有攻击性。
She's always really aggressive when she's the killer.
那就这样吧。什么?不，我不是。
There you go. What? No, I am not.
你就是在说谎。
You're lying.
你撒谎的时候声音总是很高。
Your voice always goes really high when you lie.
不,它不是。我…它……我已经……
No, it doesn't. I... it... I've...
这绝对是大卫。你喊什么?
It's definitely David. Why are you yelling?
那就太明显了
That would be so fucking obvious
如果我是凶手，但我不是
if I were the killer, which I'm not.
我觉得你在自掘坟墓
I think you're digging yourself
塞进一个小洞里，戴夫。
into a little hole here, Dave.
大卫:伙计们，上帝啊……
David: Guys, Jesus Christ...
最好的防守是有力的进攻。
The best defense is a good offense.
嘿，你闭嘴。你不应该说话。你死了。
Hey, you shut up. You're not supposed to talk. You're dead.
死人是不应该说话的。
The dead are actually not supposed to speak.
哦,是的,你……对不起，宝贝，你不能。这是一个规则。
Oh, yeah, you... sorry, baby, you can't. It's a rule.
哦，我的。是啊，别说话。住嘴。
Oh, my b. Yeah, no talking. Pack it up.
大卫:那是什么意思，格雷格?
David: What the fuck does that even mean, Greg?
有什么事吗?
What's up?
“最好的防守就是良好的进攻。”
"The best defense is a good offense."
那是什么……这是什么意思?
What does that... What does that mean?
要知道，最好的防守就是进攻。
Oh, you know, the best defense is a good offense.
什么……这是什么意思呢?
What... What does it mean, though?
嗯,嗯…
Uh, well...
,嗯…这意味着最好的防御
It, um... it means that the best defense
是很好的进攻。
is a good offense.
对，对，我听到了。
Right, right, I heard you.
但是，这对你意味着什么，格雷格?喜欢……
But, what does it mean to you, Greg? Like...
我不知道，你能详细说明一下吗?
I don't know, could you elaborate on it for us?
分解它。
Break it down.
是的,当然。
Yeah, sure.
嘿，看体育界，有…
So, hey, look in sports, there's...
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
你真是个混蛋。
You are such a fucking dick.
嘿，这是个教育的时刻。
Hey, this is a teaching moment.
哦,我明白了。
Oh, I see.
你在耍我。
You're fucking with me.
不。不,
No. No,
我没跟你开玩笑，格雷格。
I'm not fucking with you, Greg.
我只是在玩。
I'm just having fun.
我们都玩得很开心。
We're all just having a good time.
对不对?
Right, guys?
格雷格?
Right, Greg?
我们只是在玩。
We're just having fun.
你知道的,
You know,
我想我该去睡觉了。
I think it's time for me to put myself to bed.
乔丹:哦，得了吧，格雷格。艾丽斯:格雷格,没有。
Jordan: Oh, come on, Greg. Alice: Greg, no.
晚安,格雷格。
Good night, Greg.
你们玩得开心。
You kids have fun.
回头见，玩家。
Sophie: Catch you later, player.
大卫:顺便说一下，
David: By the way,
我能让大家注意一下吗
can I just point all of our attention
艾玛什么都没说
to the fact that Emma hasn't said a fucking word.
哇，你说得对。
Alice: Whoa, you're right.
哇,她没有!
Whoa, she hasn't!
大卫:我只是指出了显而易见的事实。这是所有。
David: I'm just pointing out the obvious. That's all.
看，她在做吞咽动作。
Look, she's doing that swallowing thing.
她一紧张就这么干!
She always does that when she's fucking nervous!
爱丽丝:哦，天哪!快看,快看!
Alice: Oh, my god! Look, look!
我的天，你做到了。你吞下它。
Oh, my god, you're doing it. You're swallowing it.
我不是。艾丽斯:你。
I'm not. Alice: You are.
好吧，我爱你，但你咽下去的时候，
Okay, I love you, but when you swallow,
只是他妈的……喜欢,为什么?
it's just fucking... Like, why?
吞咽是正常的。
Swallowing is normal.
这是很正常的事。大卫:是的……
It's a normal thing to do. David: Yeah...
它非常UN-attractive。我不知道你为什么这么做?
It's very UN-attractive. I don't know why you do it?
哦,我的上帝。所以你们才从来不做爱吗?
Oh, my god. Is that why you guys never have sex?
什么?爱丽丝。
What? Alice.
什么?这不是一件坏事。有些人经常做爱。
What? It's not a bad thing. Some people have sex a lot.
有些人更少。
Some people have it less.
爱丽丝，你在说什么?我们所做的。
Alice, what are you talking about? We do.
我有很多。一些……
I have it a lot. Some...
你他妈的…苏菲:哦，天哪。
Are you fucking... Sophie: Oh, my god.
你他妈是在背着我说我们吗?
Are you fucking talking about us behind my back?
不。是的。
No. Yes.
艾玛:没有。是的。
Emma: No. Yes.
不,我不是。
No, I'm not.
我不是!我不是。
I'm not! I'm not.
我只是…大卫:那太好了。
I just... David: That's just great.
艾玛:不,我……我们……我…你从来没有真正…我…
Emma: No, I... we... I... you never really... I...
我不…你总是在欺骗我。
I don't... You're always gaslighting me.
“煤气灯,闭嘴。这个词太蠢了。
"Gaslight," shut up. It's a fucking dumb word.
原谅我吗?
Excuse me?
煤气灯是最常被使用的词之一，
Gaslight is, like, one of the most over used words ever,
就像，到了毁灭的地步。
to, like, the point of annihilation.
好吧，这只是事实而已
Okay, it doesn't mean anything other than the fact
比如，你在网上阅读。
that, like, you read the Internet.
或者，“恭喜你，你有推特账号了。”
Or, like, "congrats, you have a Twitter account."
这他妈太逊了。
Ugh, that is so fucking lame.
大卫:“煤气灯”，算了吧。
David: "Gaslight," get over it.
下一个是什么?你要叫我自恋狂?
Like what's next? You're gonna call me a narcissist?
还是白人至上主义的小兵?
Or a foot soldier of, like, the white supremacy?
就像，来吧，他妈的，更原创一点。
Like, come on, fucking, be more original.
苏菲:跛。
Sophie: Lame.
大卫:什么?我只是说，这就是我要说的，
David: What? I'm just saying, that, this is what I'm saying,
她他妈脑子里一点想法都没有
she doesn't have a thought in her fucking head
其他人没这么说过。
that hasn't been said by anybody else.
没有什么不是命中注定的。
Nothing that isn't preordained.
爱丽丝:大卫，你太刻薄了。
Alice: David, that's really mean.
看,她在哭。
Look, she's crying.
大卫:什么?
David: What?
为什么大家都那样看着我?
Why is everybody looking at me like that?
这不是她真正的哭声。
This is not her real cry.
大卫我投票。
I vote David.
是的,我也是。
Yeah, me too.
你他妈说真的吗?
Are you fucking serious?
伙计们,这是艾玛。
Guys, it's Emma.
她是一个女演员。她的表演。
She's an actress. She's acting.
第三。
Third.
大卫:哇，真他妈令人惊讶。
David: Wow, how fucking surprising.
看你颤抖的上嘴唇。
Yeah, look at your quivering upper lip.
就像，我们都没在《海达·盖博勒》里见过你。去你妈的。
Like, we all didn't see you in hedda gabler. Fuck you.
是的,是的,是的……第四。
Yeah, yeah, yup... fourth.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
他妈的这个游戏!
Fuck this game!
艾丽斯:天啊。
Alice: Holy shit.
人际关系真的很复杂。
Relationships can be really complicated.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我很好。你确定吗?
I'm fine. Are you sure?
我很好。我100%罚款。你确定吗，宝贝?
I'm fine. I'm 100% fine. Are you sure, baby?
是的。让我们玩。
Yes. Let's play.
噢!
Ow!
爱丽丝:哇，不错。
Alice: Wow, good one.
乔丹:她突然喜欢上这项运动了。
Jordan: All of a sudden she loves the game.
爱丽丝:太疯狂了。
Alice: That was crazy.
把它给我。
Give it to me.
乔丹:该死的!
Jordan: Damn!
艾丽斯:啊!哦,我的上帝!
Alice: Ah! Oh, my god!
埃玛:那是什么?
Emma: What was that?
爱丽丝:搞什么鬼?乔丹:是灯的问题吗?
Alice: What the fuck? Jordan: Is that the lights?
埃玛:那是什么?
Emma: What was that?
苏菲:哦，天哪。埃玛:是暴风雨造成的吗?
Sophie: Oh, my god. Emma: Was that from the storm?
苏菲:哦，天哪。我打赌是大卫干的。
Sophie: Oh, my god. I bet you that it was David.
大卫!乔丹:不是大卫。来吧。
David! Jordan: It's not David. Come on.
我发短信他。
I'm texting him.
大卫，你在耍我们吗?
David, are you fucking with us?
把灯打开。
Turn the lights back on.
嘿，有人有电话吗?
Hey, does anybody have service?
不!
No!
等等，我的坏了。
Ugh, wait, mine's not working.
好吧，我想WiFi也坏了。
Okay, I think the WiFi is also down.
天啊，我要杀了他。
Oh, my god, i'm gonna fucking kill him.
太棒了!大卫!
Great! David!
大卫!这真是太他妈可爱了!
David! This is real fucking cute!
乔丹:索菲，他能把车库的发电机关掉吗?
Jordan: Soph, can he disable the generator from garage,
或者地下室，或者其他什么地方?
or the basement, or whatever?
我不知道。
I don't know.
大卫!
David!
好吧，我去打开断路器。
Okay, well, I'm gonna go and flip the breaker.
它在车库还是在地下室?
Is it in the garage or is it in the basement?
大卫!乔丹:大学二年级生?
David! Jordan: Soph?
啊,什么?乔丹:好的,等等。
Huh, what? Jordan: Okay, whatever.
好了，我再去拿些手电筒。
Okay, I'm gonna go get some more flashlights.
埃玛:我要去洗手间。
Emma: I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
洗手间在哪里?
Where is a bathroom?
在楼下，右手边第一个门。
Um, uh, downstairs, first door on your right.
蜜蜂:去那里。
Bee: Going there.
苏菲:大卫吗?
Sophie: David?
大卫，你在耍我们吗?
David, are you fucking with us?
我是说另一个楼梯。
I meant the other stairs.
大卫!大卫!
David! David!
的帮助!别人的帮助!
Help! Somebody help!
不,不,不。
No, no, no.
爱丽丝:到底发生了什么事?
Alice: What the fuck happened?
哦,我的上帝!为什么会……
Oh, my god! Why would...
乔丹:检查他的脉搏。搞什么鬼?
Jordan: Check his pulse. Sophie: What the fuck?
乔丹:哦,他妈的!哦,我的上帝!
Jordan: Oh, fuck! Oh, my god!
把他的头抬起来!
Hold his head up!
哦,我的上帝!他妈的!
Oh, my god! Fuck!
他妈的!爱丽丝:他要死了吗?
Fuck! Alice: Is he dying?
把他的头抬起来!艾玛:来吧，宝贝，坚持住。
Hold his head up! Emma: Come on, baby, hold on.
他的脖子怎么了?
Sophie: What the fuck happened to his neck?
我爱你，大卫。大便。
I love you, David. Shit.
爱丽丝:发生什么事了?
Alice: What is happening?
狗屎!
Shit!
爱丽丝:你在做什么?我打电话911 !
Alice: What are you doing? I'm calling 911!
哦,我的上帝!你有服务吗?
Oh, my god! You have service?
他妈的,不!你呢?
Fuck, no! Do you?
不!乔丹:狗屎!
No! Jordan: Shit!
你要去哪里?固定电话!
Where are you going? Landline!
我们要转移他的尸体吗?
We should move his body?
为什么?我不知道。因为他是……
Why? I don't know. Because he's...
爱丽丝:不，你不能移动他。
Alice: No, you can't move him.
你看svu >了吗?的证据。
Did you watch svu? It's evidence.
的什么?艾丽斯:原因!
Of what? Alice: Cause!
固定电话?不，没有联系。
Landline? No, there's no connection.
苏菲，你的钥匙呢?
Sophie, where are your keys?
索菲，你的钥匙在哪里?
Your keys, Sophie, where are they?
它们在口袋里。
They're in the pocket.
它们在她的口袋里……在哪里?该死的帮助!
They're in her pocket... Where? Fucking help!
爱丽丝:你要去哪里?
Alice: Where are you going?
我要去车上了。爱丽丝:去车上?为什么?
I'm going to the car. Alice: To the car? Why?
去找人帮忙。
To get some fucking help.
等等，你有驾照吗?
Wait, do you have a license?
她没有驾照吗?
Doesn't she not have a license?
我不知道。我不这么想。
I don't know. I don't think so.
艾丽斯:他妈的!蜜蜂:他死了!
Alice: Fuck! Bee: He's dead!
你必须离开!我不知道!
You have to go! I don't know!
他停止了呼吸!
He stopped breathing!
乔丹:分支!
Jordan: Branch!
爱丽丝:你得推一下油门。
Alice: You have to push the gas.
乔丹:我知道怎么开车，爱丽丝!
Jordan: I know how to fucking drive, Alice!
我看不到。乔丹:电池没电了吗?
I can't see. Jordan: Is the battery dead?
蜜蜂:噢,不…乔丹:什么?
Bee: Oh, no... Jordan: What?
我，我想我把灯留在镜子上了。
I, I think I left the light on, on the mirror.
哦，上帝啊。
Alice: Oh, Jesus Christ.
我们他妈该怎么办?
Emma: What the fuck are we supposed to do?
蜜蜂:等等，你的车呢?
Bee: Wait, where are your cars?
爱丽丝:我们……我们只有一辆车。
Alice: We... We only have one car.
麦克斯把我们都接走了，然后就走了!
Max picked us all up and he fucking left!
乔丹:操，操，操!
Jordan: Fuck, fuck, fuck!
麦克斯随时都可能来，对吧?
Max will probably be here any minute, right?
约旦在哪里?
Where's Jordan?
她去检查发电机，我…
She went to check the generator, I...
他到底在干什么?
What the fuck was he doing?
你在说什么?他在干什么?
What are you talking about? Sophie: Fuck was he doing?
他他妈为什么在暴风雨里在外面?
Why the fuck was he outside in the storm?
乔丹:嘿!是我，让我进去!
Jordan: Hey! It's me, let me in!
我发现这一点。
I found this.
在外面的泥里。
Outside in the mud.
苏菲:别碰它
Sophie: Don't touch it
如果停电了安保系统还能用吗?
um, does the security system work if the power goes out?
嗯…
Um...
是啊，是啊，是啊。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it does.
大卫的爸爸向我们解释过。
David's dad explained it to us.
没有密码谁也进不去。
Nobody can get in without the code.
麦克斯有密码。
Well, Max has the code.
所以…马克斯不会…
So... Max wouldn't...
我只是想问，他到底在哪?
I'm just saying, like, where the fuck is he?
昨晚之后他不会回来了吧?
Couldn't he have come back after last night?
爱丽丝,停止。
Alice, stop.
昨晚发生了什么事?
What happened last night?
没什么。艾丽斯:没有。
Nothing. Alice: No.
我们做了蘑菇
We did shrooms
麦克斯告诉所有人他爱上了艾玛
and Max told everybody that he was in love with Emma.
大卫当时觉得很美，
Which David thought was beautiful in the moment,
但也许不是今天。
but maybe not today.
爱丽丝，这根本不重要。
Alice, that literally doesn't fucking matter at all.
格雷格在哪里?他在哪里?
Where is Greg? Where is he?
什么?乔丹:格雷格在哪里?
What? Jordan: Where is Greg?
我…
I...
他说他要去睡觉了。
He said he was going to bed.
所以我猜他在睡觉。
So my guess would be that he's sleeping.
好吧，你不觉得有点奇怪吗
Okay, don't you think it's a little bit strange
他还没醒过来吗?
that he hasn't, like, woken up yet?
约旦,
Jordan,
你想说什么?
what are you trying to say.
也许我们该去看看他。
Maybe we should just go check on him.
爱丽丝:不，不，不。
Alice: No, no, no.
乔丹……
Jordan...
你在做什么?乔丹……乔丹。
What are you doing? Jordan... Jordan.
你在干什么!
What are you doing!
我保持安全。艾丽斯:真的吗?
I'm staying safe. Alice: Really?
因为看起来你在抓东西
Because it looks like you're grabbing
拿把切肉刀去找我男朋友!
a fucking meat cleaver to go look for my boyfriend!
哇。男朋友吗?
Wow. Boyfriend?
这是我第一次听你这么叫他。
That's the first time I've heard you call him that.
这太疯狂了。
That's crazy.
爱丽丝:别这么泼辣。
Alice: Don't be such a bitch.
乔丹:爱丽丝，我只是在保护自己，好吗?
Jordan: Alice, I'm literally just protecting myself, okay?
提醒你一下，我们的朋友已经死了。
Let me remind you, our friend is dead.
所以，如果你能，不要把情况升级…
So, if you could just, like, not escalate the situation...
我不升级。你拿着刀
I'm not escalating. You're holding the knife
你说话的时候还在动你的手。
and you're moving your hands while you talk.
爱丽丝，你认识格雷格多久了?
Alice, how long have you known Greg?
喜欢……
Like...
长。
Long.
爱丽丝。
Alice.
啊…
Ugh...
我不知道具体要多久。
I don't know exactly how long.
我…喜欢……
I... Like...
两个星期。
Two weeks.
乔丹:好吧,嗯…
Jordan: Okay, uh...
你对格雷格了解多少，爱丽丝?
What do you know about Greg, Alice?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
乔丹:你对他了解多少?
Jordan: What do you know about him?
天啊，伙计们!
Oh, my god, guys!
苏菲:哦，天哪!放松。停!
Sophie: Oh, my god! Relax. Stop!
停!停!我知道他是个好人，好吗?
Stop! Stop! I know that he's a good person, okay?
他本质上是个好人。
He's fundamentally a good person.
他不会这么做的。喜欢,不。
He wouldn't do this. Like, no.
你知道他的中间名吗?你知道他住在哪里吗?
Do you know his middle name? Do you know where he lives?
你知道他赚了多少钱吗?
Do you know how much fucking money he makes?
你知道他姓什么吗，爱丽丝?
Do you know his last name, Alice?
我知道很多。
I know a lot.
我们的第一次约会是在……在酒吧。
Our first date was at... Was at a bar.
他喝了大概中等量的酒…
He drank, like, a medium amount...
乔丹:好吧,爱丽丝……停止。他喜欢大自然。
Jordan: Okay, Alice... stop. He likes nature.
乔丹:他的中间名是什么?
Jordan: What is his middle name?
他是天秤座的月亮。乔丹:他住在哪里?
He's a libra moon. Jordan: Where does he live?
你不问你的中间名是什么!
You don't ask what your middle name is!
好吧?很长一段时间。乔丹:哦……他妈的!
Okay? For a really long time. Jordan: Oh... fuck!
他是天秤座的月亮。这说明了很多!
He's a libra moon. That says a lot!
他妈的!
Fuck!
格雷格!嘘!
Greg! Shh!
爱丽丝:什么?你刚说我们在找格雷格!
Alice: What? You just said we're looking for Greg!
好吧，别他妈的，爱丽丝…
Okay, well don't fucking, Alice...
格雷格!你能到厨房来一趟吗?
Greg! Can you come into the kitchen?
我们需要你帮忙。
We need you for a second.
闭嘴。别朝我挥刀!
Shut up. Stop waving the knife at me!
他妈的。你让我…
Fuck. You're making me...
停。停。格雷格!
Stop. Stop. Greg!
停。停下来。只是安静。
Stop. Just stop. Just be quiet.
停。停止。
Stop. Stop.
格雷格!不喜欢。放松。
Greg! Don't. Relax.
别抓我的嘴。放松。放松。放松。
Don't grab my mouth. Relax. Relax. Relax.
你沉默我。哦,我的上帝。
You're silencing me. Oh, my god.
滚开。好了,停止。
Get the fuck off. Okay, stop.
爱丽丝:别再那样抓我了。
Alice: Don't grab me like that again.
她拿着刀朝我冲过来。
And she came at me with a knife.
乔丹:对不起……艾丽斯:后退。
Jordan: I'm sorry... Alice: Back off.
好的,巴克!
Okay, buck!
等待,艾玛在哪儿?
Wait, where's Emma?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
乔丹:艾玛?
Jordan: Emma?
艾玛?
Emma?
伙计们,
Guys,
也许是艾玛干的
maybe Emma could have done it.
她非常生大卫的气。
She was really pissed at David.
爱丽丝，搞什么鬼?
Sophie: Alice, what the fuck?
艾玛不会那么做的。
Sophie: Emma wouldn't do that.
她极为震惊。
She was devastated.
她好像恐慌症发作了。
She's having, like, a full-on panic attack.
是啊，但她是个演员。
Yeah, but she's an actress.
她的表演。记得海达·高布乐吗?
She's acting. Remember hedda gabler?
好吧，不是我刻薄
Okay, not to be mean,
但是她在hedda gabler.
but she wasn't that good in hedda gabler.
这是我的房间。
This is my room.
所以打开它。
So open it.
你打开它。
You open it.
你不是说"格雷格不会这么做的"吗
What happened to, "Greg would never do this?"
他不会。好吧，打开它。
He wouldn't. Okay, so open it.
我马上就会。
I will in one second.
我要去。
I'm going to.
他不在这里。
Sophie: He's not here.
索菲，房子里有枪吗?
Soph, are there any guns in the house?
枪支?
Guns?
不。不可能。
No. No way.
大卫的爸爸可能是个混蛋，但他的政治立场是对的。
David's dad can be a dick, but his politics check out.
乔丹:男人…
Jordan: Guys...
这他妈是什么?
What the fuck is this?
嗯…但是…
Uh... but...
他想为飓风做好准备。他……
He wanted to be prepared for the hurricane. He...
他为什么绕着房子转
Sophie: Why did he circle the fucking house
在他该死的地图上?
on his fucking map?
乔丹:我们得在他之前找到艾玛。
Jordan: We have to find Emma before he does.
索菲:好的。
Sophie: Okay.
乔丹:接下来我们去我的房间看看。
Jordan: Let's check my room next.
乔丹:我不认为他藏在我的胸罩里。
Jordan: I don't think he's hiding in my bra.
艾丽斯:男人……
Alice: Guys...
到这里来。
Come here.
天啊，艾玛。
Oh, my god, Emma.
艾玛。
Emma.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
埃玛:怎么了?你们在做什么?
Emma: What's going on? What are you guys doing?
你吓到我了发生什么事了?
You scared me what's happening?
这里太热了。
It's so hot in here.
那是什么?
What is that?
阿普唑仑。你想要一个吗?对，给我一个。
Xanax. Do you want one? Yeah, give me one.
你想要一个吗?索菲娅:不。
You want one? Sophie: No.
乔丹:嘿，你拿着这个。
Jordan: Hey, you take this.
为什么?乔丹:我去找格雷格。
Why? Jordan: I'm gonna find Greg.
格雷格,为什么?马克斯在哪儿?
Greg, why? Where's Max?
也许是麦克斯干的。也许他在这儿。
Maybe Max did it. Maybe he is here.
麦克斯非常生大卫的气。
Max was really angry at David.
我是认真的，他看起来要
I'm serious, he looked like he was gonna
做些真正操蛋的事。
do something really fucked up.
乔丹:爱丽丝!闭嘴。我只是说。
Jordan: Alice! Shut up. I'm just saying.
马克斯不会。
Max would never.
我们去找格雷格吧。
Let's go find Greg.
好的。
Okay.
乔丹:……
Jordan: What the...
他妈的什么?爱丽丝:哦，天哪。
What the fuck? Alice: Oh, my god.
他脸上是什么鬼东西?
Sophie: What the hell is on his face?
这是他的光疗面具。他患有季节性抑郁症。
It's his light therapy mask. He has seasonal depression.
乔丹:我们走吧。
Jordan: Let's go.
嘿…嘘……
Hey... shh...
艾丽斯:格雷格。
Alice: Greg.
有什么事吗?乔丹:你去哪儿了?
What's up? Jordan: Where have you been?
嗯?
Huh?
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
哦,我,嗯…
Oh, I, uh...
我睡不着,
I couldn't sleep,
所以我就下来锻炼了。
so I came down here to do my exercises.
爱丽丝:你为什么不回答我?
Alice: Why didn't you answer me?
你是找我吗?
Were you calling for me?
艾丽斯:是的。
Alice: Yeah.
我…我戴着耳机。
I... I had my headphones in.
你们还在玩狼人游戏吗?
Are you guys still playing werewolf?
艾丽斯:格雷格!
Alice: Greg!
停!停止它!
Stop! Stop it!
好吧。
All right.
我该怎么办，嗯?
What am I supposed to do, huh?
你怎么不告诉我们，该死的格雷格?
Why don't you tell us, fucking Greg?
格雷格:那是我的应急包吗?那是一把刀吗?
Greg: Is that my go bag? Is that a knife?
你为什么要带个应急包?
Why did you bring a go bag?
飓风吗?看吧，我告诉过你。
The hurricane? See, I told you.
你为什么绕着房子转
Sophie: Why did you circle the fucking house
在你该死的地图上?
on your fucking map?
这是怎么呢大卫已经死了。
What's going on? David is dead.
他的身体在外面。
His body is outside.
大卫的身体。等等,什么?
David's body. Wait, what?
你为什么要杀大卫?
Why did you kill David?
你杀了我男朋友。
You murdered my boyfriend.
不,不。大卫杀了我。对吧?
No, no. David killed me. Right?
乔丹:这不是开玩笑，格雷格。
Jordan: This isn't a joke, Greg.
大卫已经死了。有人割了他的喉咙。
David is dead. Somebody slit his throat.
什么?用一把该死的剑，
What? Sophie: With a fucking sword,
你这个变态!
you fucking sick fuck!
哦……
Oh...
你们在耍我吗?
You guys are fucking with me?
你们在耍我。
Oh, you guys are fucking with me.
他妈的!
Fuck!
可爱。
Cute.
不!
No!
好的。
Okay.
每个人都需要深呼吸。
Everyone needs to take a deep breath.
爱丽丝。
Alice.
苏菲:把刀还给我!
Sophie: Give me my knife back!
这他妈是怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on?
我不知道!
I don't know!
放下武器。乔丹:你把它放下。
Put down the weapons. Jordan: You put it down.
现在!
Now!
在地板上!
On the floor!
乔丹:好吧,好吧。这个怎么样?
Jordan: Okay, okay. How about this?
把它下来。乔丹:好，好，好。
Put it down. Jordan: Okay, okay, okay.
好的，我们会把它们放下的。
Okay, we'll put them down.
我们会把…我们都要把它们放下。
We'll put... we'll all put them down.
对吧?你把你的放下，我们就把它们放下。
Right? We'll put them down if you put yours down.
我们会把它们放下的。
We'll put them down.
好的。
Okay.
好的。是的,请,请。
Okay. Yeah, please, please.
这看起来很公平。艾丽斯:是的。
That seems fair. Alice: Yeah.
好的。
Okay.
将下来。
Putting it down.
我们很好。是的。
We're good. Yeah.
好吧，这很好。
Okay, this is good.
好吧。
All right.
乔丹!你还好吗?
Jordan! Are you okay?
噢!艾丽斯:停!停!
Ow! Alice: Stop! Stop!
请停止!格雷格:爱丽丝?
Please stop! Greg: Alice?
艾丽斯:停止。停!
Alice: Stop. Stop!
不!不!
No! No!
苏菲!不。不不不，苏菲!
Sophie! No. No, no, no, Sophie!
格雷格:母亲笨蛋。
Greg: Mother fucker.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
爱丽丝:这不对。
Alice: This isn't right.
不是他干的。
He didn't do it.
爱丽丝，你怎么知道的?你怎么知道是他干的?
Alice, how do you know? How do you that know he did?
听着，我的意思是…
Look, I mean, like...
如果你看着我们所有人，
If you look at all of us, like,
在纸面上,从逻辑上讲,
on paper, logically,
他最有可能实施暴力行为。
he is the most likely to commit an act of violence.
在纸上?
On paper?
你他妈到底在说什么?
What the fuck are you even talking about?
我是说，他是唯一的一个
I mean, he's the only one
谁在军队服役，对吧?所以…
who served in the military, right? So...
什么?
What?
乔丹:他是兽医。
Jordan: He's a vet.
对吧?像伊拉克?还是……
Right? Like Iraq? Or...
埃玛:不，我以为是阿富汗。
Emma: No, I thought it was Afghanistan.
他是个兽医。
He was a veterinarian.
他是兽医的助手。
He was a veterinarian's assistant.
你他妈说真的吗?
Are you fucking serious right now?
埃玛:那你为什么叫他大兵乔?
Emma: Then why did you call him g.I. Joe?
因为…你见过他吗?
Because... have you seen him?
不管怎样，不管怎样，
Well, regardless, either way,
在我们所有人当中，他是最大的未知数。
like, out of all of us, he is the biggest unknown.
我们认识很久了。
We've known each other forever.
爱丽丝:乔丹，你想做什么?
Alice: Jordan, what are you trying to do?
乔丹:我不是……我没想做什么。
Jordan: I'm not... I'm not trying to do anything.
爱丽丝:他死了，好吗?
Alice: He's dead, okay?
他死了。我们杀了他。
He's dead. We killed him.
她杀了他。
She killed him.
去换件衬衫。
Go change your shirt.
埃玛:我们得走了。我们得离开这里。
Emma: We need to leave. We need to get out of here.
我们没有车。
We don't have a car.
好吧，我走着去。艾玛,停下来。
Okay, I'm going to walk. Emma, stop.
你是什么意思?你不能就这么…
What do you mean? You can't just fucking...
乔丹:艾玛，你真是荒无人烟。
Jordan: Emma, you're literally in the middle of nowhere.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
爱丽丝:我是说，我们任何人都有可能。
Alice: I mean, it could have been any of us.
灯灭的时候我们都散了。
We all scattered when the lights went out.
我是说，也可能是麦克斯，好吗?
I mean, it could have been Max, okay?
爱丽丝，你不知道你在说什么。
Alice, you don't know what you are talking about.
因为你，他打了大卫一拳。
He punched David in the face because of you.
就因为麦克斯爱上我了
Just because Max is in love with me
并不意味着他会杀了大卫
doesn't mean he would kill David.
你他妈有什么毛病啊?
Oh, what the fuck is wrong with you?
艾玛:什么?
Emma: What?
这不是你和麦克斯的事。
This is not about you and Max.
你为什么这么刻薄?
Why are you being so mean?
因为我很难过，艾玛。
Because I'm upset, Emma.
我难过是因为有人杀了我最好的朋友。
I'm upset because somebody killed my best friend.
苏菲，你用了吗?我相信你在做
Sophie, did you use? I can believe you're making
这对你。
this about you.
我也很难过，好吗?我也怕。
I'm sad, too, okay? I'm scared, too.
我非常爱他。
I loved him so much.
看起来不像。
It didn't seem like it.
什么?苏菲:看起来是这样
What? Sophie: It seemed like
你喜欢有个男朋友。
you loved having a boyfriend.
你喜欢舒适的感觉。
And you loved feeling comfortable.
但是，不，你不爱他。
But, no, you did not love him.
你根本就不喜欢他。
You didn't even fucking like him.
你只是太害怕了，不敢做任何事。
You were just too scared to do anything about it.
所以你多待了三年
So you stayed for three years longer than you should have
因为你是个懦夫。
because you're a coward.
不,我不是。
No, I'm not.
我不是。
I'm not.
我不是。对吧?我…
I'm not. Right? I...
你……你这么有毒。
You're... you're so toxic.
艾玛,冷静下来。你。
Emma, calm down. You are.
不!不，我不会…
No! No, I'm not gonna...
你太毒了。
You are so toxic.
说实话，当你从地球上消失的时候，
And, honestly, when you fell off the face of the earth,
大卫是松了一口气。
David was relieved.
不用再和你打交道了，他松了一口气。
He was relieved he didn't have to deal with you anymore.
我真希望他们把你的头砍下来，
I wish they had chopped off your head instead,
你这个没骨气的混蛋。
you spineless piece of shit.
索菲娅。
Sophie.
我的天啊。
Alice: Jesus fucking Christ.
艾玛。
Emma.
艾玛,来吧。等待。
Emma, come on. Wait.
等待。艾丽斯:艾玛。
Wait. Alice: Emma.
艾玛。
Emma.
乔丹:你说得真好，苏苏。
Jordan: That was real nice, soph.
家伙……
Guys...
蜜蜂他妈的在哪里?
Where the fuck is bee?
索菲娅:艾玛。
Sophie: Emma.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉。
I'm really sorry.
我现在真是一团糟。
I'm so fucked up right now.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
好吧?就好像，事情开始发生了……
Okay? It was just, like, things started coming...
这不正是你想要的吗?
Isn't that what you wanted?
是的，艾玛，这就是我想要的。
Yeah, Emma, that's what I wanted.
这正是我想要的。
That's what I was in the mood for.
非常感谢。他妈的什么?
Thank you very much. What the fuck?
耶稣基督!
Jesus Christ!
你总以为每个人都爱你。
You always think everyone is in love with you.
它是如此疯狂。我…
It's so crazy. I...
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你要这个吗?
Do you want this?
是的。
Yeah.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
确定。
Sure.
艾丽斯:蜜蜂?
Alice: Bee?
大学二年级生吗?
Soph?
乔丹:艾玛?
Jordan: Emma?
的帮助!
Help!
乔丹!
Jordan!
的帮助!
Help!
的帮助。乔丹:你在哪里?
Help. Jordan: Where are you?
的帮助!请帮助!的帮助!
Help! Please, help! Help!
的帮助!的帮助!的帮助!
Help! Help! Help!
艾玛。
Emma.
乔丹:哦，天哪。艾丽斯:艾玛。
Jordan: Oh, my god. Alice: Emma.
哦,我的上帝。哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
发生了什么事?我不知道!
What happened? I don't know!
我不知道。
I don't know.
别碰她!我只是想…
Don't touch her! I'm just trying to...
不喜欢。不!弄清楚发生了什么。
Don't. No! Figure out what happened.
乔丹:我不碰她怎么知道?
Jordan: How am I supposed to know if I don't touch her?
不要，不要，不要。
Alice: Don't, just don't, just don't.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
爱丽丝:我听到了什么。
Alice: I heard something.
嗯,也许她……
Um, maybe she...
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
她摔倒了，也许她绊倒了?艾丽斯:没有。
She fell, maybe she tripped? Alice: No.
不,不。她……
No, no. She...
她……她被推了，好吗?
She... she got pushed, okay?
她推。我告诉过你不是格雷格!
She was pushed. I told you it wasn't Greg!
乔丹:她死了你高兴吗?
Jordan: Are you happy that she's dead?
不，但我告诉过你不是格雷格!
No, but I told you it wasn't Greg!
我做了……我告诉过你了。
I did... I did tell you.
爱丽丝:你没看到发生了什么吗?
Alice: Don't you see what's happening?
什么?
What?
凶手是谁?
Who was the killer?
什么?
What?
凶手是谁?
Who was the killer?
在游戏中?
In the game?
它遵循同样的模式。
It's following the same pattern.
死亡。
The deaths.
请……求你了，别说了，求你了!
Please... please, just stop talking, please!
大卫,格雷格,艾玛。
David, Greg, Emma.
乔丹:没有。是的!
Jordan: No. Yes!
他妈的是的,乔丹!乔丹:没有。
Fucking yes, Jordan! Jordan: No.
不，不是同一个模式。
No, it's not following the same pattern.
格雷格死了，然后我们处决了大卫。
Greg died and then we executed David.
但在现实生活中，大卫死了，然后我们…
But in real life, David died and then we...
好吧，但是格雷格，大卫，艾玛。格雷格,大卫,艾玛。
Okay, but Greg, David, Emma. Greg, David, Emma.
不然为什么会有人把她留在那里
I mean, why else would somebody leave her there
除非他们想让我们找到她?
unless they wanted us to find her?
他们为什么要我们找到她?
Why would they want us to find her?
因为他们在玩一个变态的游戏。
Because they're playing a sick fucking game.
好吗?
Okay?
凶手是谁?我不是凶手。
Who was the killer? I wasn't the killer.
爱丽丝，你他妈嗑嗨了。
Alice, you're fucking coked out.
你嗑嗨了，好吗?我们都喝高了。
You're coked out, okay? We're all coked out.
我不是。
I'm not.
你化了妆吗?
Are you wearing make up?
我…我在楼上换我的…
I... I was upstairs, changing my...
爱丽丝:你看起来很奇怪。
Alice: You look weird.
这是谁的毛衣?
Whose sweater is this?
我在楼上找到的。
I found it upstairs.
你认识她多久了?
How long have you known her?
停止,爱丽丝。
Stop, Alice.
你是谁?
Who are you?
什么?你出现在这里，
What? You show up here,
开始对我男朋友微笑。
start smiling at my boyfriend.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你的声音在颤抖。
Your voice is trembling.
不。不。是的。它是。
No. No. Yeah. It is.
乔丹:我在谷歌上搜索过你。
Jordan: I googled you.
没人叫你的名字
And there was nobody with your name
今年毕业于犹他州立大学。
who graduated from Utah state this year.
根本就没有你的出勤记录。
There's literally no record of your attendance, at all.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
听着，我可以解释。
Listen, I can explain.
爱丽丝:哦，天哪。
Alice: Oh, my god.
你发现了大卫的尸体。
You discovered David's body.
不,我只是……你可能做了手脚
No, I just... You could have tampered
发电机,
with the generator,
就像你对苏菲的车做了手脚一样
just like you tampered with Sophie's car.
你说你没关灯，对吧?
You said you left the lights on, right?
你是认真的吗?我们看到你杀人了。
Are you serious? We watched you kill someone.
你真的杀了格雷格!
You literally murdered Greg!
字面上!
Literally!
字面上!你他妈的生病!
Literally! You sick fuck!
不，你疯了吗?不。冷静下来。
No, are you crazy? No. Calm down.
我们谈谈吧。谈论它呢?
Let's just talk about it. Talk about it?
蜜蜂:是的。不…不。
Bee: Yeah. No... no.
让我们好好谈谈，好吗?
Bee: Let's just talk about it, okay?
嗯嗯。我不想。
Mmm-mmm. I don't want to.
蜜蜂:苏菲…索菲娅。艾丽斯:不!
Bee: Sophie... Sophie. Alice: No!
蜜蜂:索菲娅。别碰她!
Bee: Sophie. Ali, ce: Do not touch her!
哇!
Whoa!
你知道吗?我不…
Alice: You know what? I don't...
我不想让你进来。
I don't want you in here.
好吧,冷静下来。
Okay, calm down.
不,我是认真的。爱丽丝!
No, seriously. Alice!
爱丽丝!我不想让你进来。
Alice! I don't want you in here.
蜜蜂:我……放松。闭嘴!闭嘴!
Bee: I... relax. Just shut up! Shut up!
我不想让你进来。
I don't want you in here.
滚出这个房间!放开我，爱丽丝。
Get out of this room! Let go of me, Alice.
滚出这个房间!
Get the fuck out of this room!
我不想再看到你的脸了。出去。
I don't want to look at your face anymore. Get out.
蜜蜂:爱丽丝，冷静。艾丽斯:我不…
Bee: Alice, calm down. Alice: I'm not...
爱丽丝:我没冷静下来。蜜蜂:放开我，爱丽丝。
Alice: I'm not calming down. Bee: Let go of me, Alice.
不，你杀了我的男朋友。
No, you killed my fucking boyfriend.
你知道吗?你知道吗?这是自卫。
You know what? You know what? It was self-defense.
艾丽斯:我……我要她出去。
Alice: I... I want her out.
乔丹，你能帮帮我吗?好吧。
Jordan, can you help me? All right.
乔丹!耶稣,爱丽丝。
Jordan! Jesus, Alice.
快把门打开!
Get the fucking door!
基督耶稣他妈的!
Jesus fucking Christ!
我不想让她进来!
I do not want her in here!
蜜蜂:放松!艾丽斯:不!
Bee: Relax! Alice: No!
苏菲!苏菲,做点什么!
Sophie! Sophie, do something!
你杀了他，滚出去!
You killed him, get out!
苏菲!艾丽斯:出去!
Sophie! Alice: Get out!
苏菲!
Sophie!
乔丹:留在这里。
Jordan: Stay here.
爱丽丝:我好饿。
Alice: I'm so hungry.
乔丹:你现在怎么会饿呢?
Jordan: How can you be hungry right now?
爱丽丝:我没想到会这样。
Alice: I wasn't planning on this.
乔丹:爱丽丝……
Jordan: Alice...
他妈的什么?你他妈怎么进来的?
What the fuck? How the fuck you get in here?
她有枪。
She has a gun.
乔丹口袋里有把枪，苏菲，
Jordan has a gun in her pocket, Sophie,
离她远点。
get away from her.
不，不，苏菲，她让人迷惑…
No, no, Sophie, she's confusing...
放开我。
Let go of me.
你在开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding me?
我没有枪。
I don't have a gun.
蜜蜂:那就把口袋里的东西都掏出来。
Bee: Then empty your pockets.
慢慢的!
Slowly!
就这些吗?
That's it?
就是这样。
That's it.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
你是凶手。
You are the killer.
在…在游戏中…我…
In the... in the game... I...
你他妈怎么进来的?
How the fuck did you get in here?
枪在哪里?我他妈没有枪。
Where is the gun? I don't have a fucking gun.
我们把所有的门都锁了。你是怎么进来的?
We locked all the doors. How did you get in?
你杀了他。
You killed him.
我为什么要杀大卫?我为什么要杀大卫?
Why would I kill David? Why would I kill David?
我为什么要杀艾玛?
Why would I kill Emma?
他们真的是我最老的朋友。
They are, literally, my oldest friends.
你他妈才刚认识他们!你怎么敢?
You just fucking met them! How dare you?
当我找到大卫时，
When I found David,
你是最后一个到那里的人。
you were the last person to get there.
你花了一些时间。这是真的。
It took you awhile. That's true.
艾玛死的时候你在哪里?
Bee: Where were you when Emma died, hmm?
你推她!闭嘴!
You pushed her! Shut up!
别听她的。你根本不知道这是怎么回事
Guy's, don't listen to her. You don't know what the fuck
你在说什么!然后，我看到了你。
you're talking about! And then, I saw you.
我看到你拿枪了。
I saw you getting the gun.
乔丹:那是谎言。
Jordan: That's a lie.
这他妈是个谎言。你就是在说谎。你是一个骗子!
That's a fucking lie. You're lying. You're a liar!
你他妈是在说谎。
You're lying through your fucking teeth.
你说的都是谎话。
You lied about everything.
你对苏菲撒了谎
You lied about everything to Sophie.
你他妈是个骗子。
You're a fucking liar.
是的,你……你确实对苏菲撒谎了。
Yeah, you... You did lie to Sophie.
好的。
Okay.
我确实上过犹他州立大学
I did go to Utah state
为一个学期。
for one semester.
但我妈妈…她的日子不好过
But my mom was... She was having a hard time
我就回家照顾她了
and I came home to take care of her.
我确实在gamehut工作过，
And I did work at gamehut,
但他们关闭了我们的店，
but they shut down our location, like,
我认识你一周后我…我一直在申请，但是…
a week after I met you. I... I've been applying, but...
我摔倒的时候你在干什么
What were you doing when I dropped
你去商场了吗?
you off at the mall?
在美食广场闲逛。我…
Hung out at the food court. I...
不想让你失望。
Didn't want to disappoint you.
我很尴尬。
I was embarrassed.
我应该告诉你的。我只是…
I should have told you. I just...
我的妈妈,她……
My mom, she...
她有……
She has...
我妈妈有边缘性人格障碍。
My mom has borderline.
爱丽丝:哦，天哪。
Alice: Oh, my god.
我很抱歉，那…
I'm so sorry, that's...
这是非常严重的。
That's really serious.
心理健康是一个非常严重的问题。
Mental health is a really serious issue.
我从来没对任何人说过，但是…
I mean, I've never actually said this to anyone, but...
但我有身体畸形。
But I have body dysmorphia.
哦,我的上帝。闭嘴，爱丽丝。
Oh, my god. Shut the fuck up, Alice.
我想告诉你的。我只是…
I wanted to tell you. I just...
我只是想让你喜欢我。
I just really wanted you to like me.
你他妈开什么玩笑。
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
乔丹，搞什么鬼?
Jordan, what the fuck?
你是说你相信吗
Are you telling me that you believe that
堆废话吗?
pile of bullshit?
这是为了激发信心吗?
Is that supposed to inspire confidence?
她妈妈有“边缘性人格障碍”。
Her mom has "borderline."
这对其他人来说不是危险信号吗?
Is that not a red fucking flag to anybody else?
这是一个很严重的问题。
That's a serious issue.
你他妈从哪弄来的?
Where the fuck did you get that?
大卫的爸爸丰富的!
David's dad's rich!
有钱人都他妈有枪，苏菲!
Rich people have fucking guns, Sophie!
我的父母很富有。他们没有枪。
My parents are rich. They don't have guns.
我是说，我们都很有钱
Well, I mean, we're all rich,
但你和大卫很有钱很有钱
but you and David are like rich, rich.
这对我来说从来都不重要……
That has never mattered to me...
你他妈给我闭嘴!
Oh, shut the fuck up!
我们甚至都不想邀请你。
We didn't even want to invite you.
我们讨论过邀请你
We debated about inviting you,
而是因为这是大卫的房子。
but because it's David's house.
我没那么说，但是…
I didn't say that, but...
不，你没有在群聊中回复我。
And, no, you did not respond in the group chat.
然后，你就带着这个变态出现了。
And then, you show up with this fucking psychopath.
别叫她精神变态，那太歧视残疾人了。
Don't call her a psychopath, that's so ableist.
去你妈的。你们配得上对方。
Fuck you. You deserve each other.
我希望她在你睡觉的时候让你窒息。
I hope she fucking suffocates you in your sleep.
爱丽丝:是啊，你在聊天中没有回复。
Alice: Yeah, you didn't reply in the chat.
大卫告诉过我
And David actually told me
你求他跟你父母谈谈
that you, like, begged him to talk to your parents
就像，再次解锁你的信任。
and, like, unlock your trust again.
这就是你来这里的原因。
And that's why you're actually here.
噢,是吗?
Oh, yeah?
是啊，他告诉你了吗
Oh, yeah, did he tell you that
当你们排在我前面的时候。
while you guys were railing lines in front of me.
你吸毒的朋友
Your addict friend
你到底在担心谁?
who you're supposedly so worried about?
我们都很担心。索菲娅:不!
We are worried. Sophie: No!
不,不,不。让我把话说清楚。
No, no, no. Let me get this straight.
好吧，让我搞清楚。
Okay, let me get this straight.
所以，当黑人女孩
So, when the black girl
有吸食可卡因的习惯，这是个问题。
has a coke habit, it's a problem.
但当她周围的人都这么做时，
But when everyone else around her does it,
包括她最好的朋友，恰好是白人
including her best friend, who happens to be white
,男,
and male,
它很好吗?
it's fine?
我理解，我是你的盟友
I understand and I'm an ally,
我完全明白…
and I totally get how it...
看上去如此。
Looks that way.
和…
And...
嗯…
Um...
约旦吗?哦,我的上帝。
Jordan? Oh, my god.
你沉迷于扮演受害者。
You are obsessed with playing the victim.
苏菲:对不起?
Sophie: Excuse me?
我不得不和你一起上了救护车
I had to ride in the ambulance with you
三次，以为你死了。
three times, thinking you were dead.
我需要帮助，我得到了帮助
I needed help and I got it
我很抱歉。你有帮助吗?
and I'm sorry. You got help?
你是说我们得向你爸告发你
You mean we had to narc on you to your fucking dad
所以他会切断你的经济来源，送你去戒毒所，
so he'd cut you off and ship you off to rehab,
而你却在不停地又踢又叫。
while you were quite literally kicking and screaming.
是的。然后你就
Yeah. And then you just
从地球上消失了。
fell off the face of the earth.
因为这就是你的工作，苏苏。
'Cause that's what you do, soph.
遇到困难的时候，你就该逃跑。
That's what you do when things get tough, you run.
你他妈跑去写回忆录了。
You ran away to go write your fucking memoirs.
这是一种创造性的非虚构作品，这是一种有效的回应
It's creative non-fiction which is a valid response
关注经济中的生活。
to life in an attention economy.
哦，去死吧。
Oh, fuck off and die.
你写小论文
You write little essays
关于你妈妈和她的伏特加。
about your mommy and her vodka.
还有你的阴部和你的感情。
And your pussy and your feelings.
还有你的感情。
And your fucking feelings.
天啊，我们都要淹死了
Oh, my god, we are all drowning
在你他妈的感觉里。
in your fucking feelings.
感觉是事实。不!不,他们不是。
Feelings are facts. No! No, they're not.
事实就是事实。
Facts are facts.
苏菲，你为什么不告诉我们?
Why did you ghost us, Sophie?
喜欢为什么?
Like why?
因为你刺激了我。
Because you fucking trigger me.
你支持我。
You enable me.
她知道吗?
Does she know?
她知道什么吗?
Sophie: Does she know what?
你恳求我
That you begged me
我来的路上顺便去趟你的公寓。
to stop at your apartment on my way up here.
我所做的。
And I did.
我们在你车里做爱。
And we fucked in your car.
她他妈的说谎。
She's fucking lying.
她在睁眼说瞎话。
She's lying through her fucking teeth.
她想扰乱你的大脑。
She's trying to get in your head.
别听她的，好吗?
Don't listen to her, okay?
检查她的短信。
Check her texts.
你疯了，乔丹。
You are unhinged, Jordan.
你缺乏同理心。
You are devoid of empathy.
你没有感情。
You have no feelings.
你想知道我为什么不能吗
Do you want to know why I could never
和你在一起过吗?
ever be with you?
因为你的时间表
Because you schedule
你日历上的所有事
everything in your fucking Google calendar,
包括性。
including sex.
因为你没有灵魂。
Because you have no soul.
乔丹:去你妈的。
Jordan: Fuck you.
你感情上受虐待。
You're emotionally abusive.
我得去接受创伤后应激障碍的治疗。
I had to go to therapy for PTSD.
你可以问爱丽丝。
You can fucking ask Alice.
是的,她做的。
Yeah, she did.
很长一段时间。
For a long time.
你讨厌爱丽丝。
You hate Alice.
不,我不喜欢。是啊，你鄙视她。
No, I don't. Yeah, you despise her.
你总是抱怨自己有多无聊
You complain constantly about how vapid
她很烦人。你讨厌她。
and annoying she is. You hate her.
你总是不停地取笑我，真可怜
It's pitiful how you won't stop making fun
她那愚蠢的播客。
of her stupid little podcast.
让她用播客吧。
Let her have the podcast.
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're talking about.
你讨厌听她的播客。
You hate listen to her podcast.
等待……
Wait...
什么?
What?
你让我们以生命发誓
And you made us swear on our lives
不要告诉任何人。
not to tell anyone.
乔丹，这是真的吗?
Jordan, is that true?
我喜欢你的播客，爱丽丝。
I like your podcast, Alice.
你的播客是关于什么的?
What is your podcast about?
和你最聪明最有趣的朋友出去玩。
Hanging out with your smartest and funniest friend.
你刚刚是在呻吟吗?
Did you just groan?
不。
No.
我说"出去玩"的时候
When I said "hanging out
"和你最聪明最有趣的朋友"
"with your smartest and funniest friend."
哦,我的上帝。像这样。像这样!
Oh, my god. Like that. Like that!
他妈的!你又来了。
Fuck! You just did it again.
不,我没有!首先,
No, I didn't! First of all,
播客需要花很多功夫，好吗?
a podcast takes a lot of work, okay?
你得组织好客人。
You have to organize the guests.
你得做个谷歌日历
You have to do a Google calendar
然后你就有了追随者。
and you build a following.
这他妈的要花很长时间!
It takes a long fucking time!
我已经研究了一段时间了!
And I've been working on it for a while!
好吗?
Okay?
然后，我说，
And then, let me say,
没人喜欢你，好吗?
that nobody likes you, okay?
没有人喜欢你!没有人喜欢你!
Nobody likes you! Nobody likes you!
你知道吗，当你喝醉了，向我哭诉，
Do you know when you're drunk and you cry to me,
“哦，恐怕没人喜欢我
"oh, I'm afraid nobody likes me
"因为我又贱又贱，我很烂"
"because I'm mean and a bitch and I suck."
你知道的，好吗?你他妈的很烂。
Well, you do, okay? You fucking suck.
我和你在一起只是出于同情
And I only hang out with you out of pity
以及我们共同历史令人窒息的重压。
and the suffocating weight of our shared history.
就这些。
And that is all.
你是如此的爱我
And you're just so in love
从你白手起家的故事来看
with your rags to riches narrative,
好像你是世界上唯一的人
like you're the only fucking person in the world
他出身贫寒。
who didn't come from money.
你知道吗?
You know what?
你的父母是中上阶层。
Your parents are upper middle class.
不,他们不是。
No, they're not.
乔丹。
Jordan.
他们是。
They are.
他们在一所大学教书。
They teach at a university.
这是公开的。
It's public.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
天啊，难怪索菲吸毒过量了。
Oh, my god, I mean, no wonder Sophie od'd.
谁能确定一个该死的电子表格的日期
Who could date a fucking spreadsheet
有优越感吗?
with a superiority complex?
就像，你真是个…
It's, like, you're such a...
噢!
Ow!
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
搞什么，乔丹?
Sophie: What the fuck, Jordan?
爱丽丝:哦，天哪。你是认真的吗?
Alice: Oh, my god. Are you serious?
你他妈是开枪打我吗?
Did you just fucking shoot me?
不。你他妈射中了我。
No. Alice: You fucking shot me.
拿着枪!
With a gun!
乔丹:不，我没有开枪打你。我…
Jordan: No, I didn't shoot you. I...
你他妈的杀了他们，你这个变态!
Alice: You fucking murdered them, you freak!
你是凶手。我就知道!
You're the murderer. I knew it!
我就知道，你就是个贱人!
I knew it, you're such a bitch!
你这个婊子!
You're such a fucking bitch!
我没有谋杀任何人。爱丽丝:是的，你说了。
I didn't murder anybody. Alice: Yes, you did.
乔丹，把枪放下。
Jordan, put the gun down.
爱丽丝:我从来没中过枪。
Alice: I've never been shot before.
真他妈疼!
It really fucking hurts!
把枪放下，拜托。
Sophie: Put the fucking gun down, please.
你这样做。是你逼我这么做的。
You did this. You made me do this.
你为什么逼我这么做?
Why did you make me do that?
你在做什么?把枪放下。
What are you doing? Put the gun down.
为什么?你为什么朝我开枪?
Why? Why did you shoot me?
乔丹:我没有开枪打你。
Jordan: I did not shoot you.
是的,你做的!那把枪!停止,停止,停止。
Yes, you did! With that gun! Stop, stop, stop.
爱丽丝,停止。停!那把枪。
Alice, stop. Stop! With that gun.
别到处挥舞了。我不是挥舞着。
Stop waving it around. I'm not waving.
不要打我。你已经开枪打我了。
Don't hit me. You already shot me.
停!别碰我。
Stop! Don't touch me.
苏菲:不，不，不!爱丽丝:拿枪来!
Sophie: No, no, no! Alice: Get the gun!
索菲娅:不!苏菲，枪!
Sophie: No! Alice: Sophie, the gun!
不!停!你踩到我腿了!
Don't! Stop! You're on my leg!
你踩到我腿了!
You're on my leg!
我想要它。把它给我!
I want it. Give it to me!
乔丹:不!苏菲:放开!
Jordan: No! Sophie: Let go!
乔丹:不!
Jordan: No!
索菲娅:噢!
Sophie: Ow!
艾丽斯:不!
Alice: No!
不!爱丽丝:把它给我。
No! Alice: Give it to me.
给我吧!给我吧!放开我!不!
Give me it! Give me it! Get off of me! No!
乔丹:他妈的放开我!
Jordan: Get the fuck off me!
下车!
Get off!
噢!我他妈的腿!
Ow! My fucking leg!
苏菲:在哪里?
Sophie: Where is it?
艾丽斯:噢!
Alice: Ow!
不是我干的。
I didn't do it.
请不要动。
Please, don't move.
你他妈的别动。
Don't you fucking move.
没关系……没事的,乔丹。
It's okay... It's okay, Jordan.
请不要这样做。
Please, don't do it.
请,只是……
Please, just...
停!不是我干的。求你了，别说了，好吗?
Stop! I didn't do it. Please, just stop, okay?
把它放下。请停止运动。
Just put it down. Please, stop moving.
请……求你了，别跟着我。
Please... please, don't follow me, please.
请……停!停止它!停止它!
Please... Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
停止,停止,停止!
Stop, stop, stop!
我们为什么要这么做?
Sophie: Why are we doing this?
乔丹:别上来。
Jordan: Don't come up here.
不,请不要。
Don't, please, don't.
苏菲:请把它放下。
Sophie: Please put it down.
乔丹:请停止。请呆在那里。
Jordan: Please stop. Please stay there.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my god.
苏菲:请……
Sophie: Please...
乔丹:停止。苏菲:我求你了……
Jordan: Stop. Sophie: I'm begging you...
别他妈上来。拜托。
Don't fucking come up here. Please.
苏菲，我是认真的，待在那别动。
Sophie, I'm serious, just stay there.
苏菲:停止。
Sophie: Stop.
只是呆在那里。请待在那里。
Just stay there. Just please stay there.
我乞求你。
I'm begging you.
请,他妈的……该死的呆在那里!他妈的!
Please, fucking... Fucking stay there! Fuck!
苏菲:蜜蜂!
Sophie: Bee!
检查她的短信。
Check her texts.
索菲娅。
Sophie.
你杀了艾玛吗?
Did you kill Emma?
不。
No.
是吗?
Did you?
不。
No.
没关系，如果是你做的。没关系。
It's okay, if you did it. It's okay.
我只是想知道。你可以告诉我。
I just want to know. You can tell me.
你杀了大卫吗?什么?
Did you kill David? What?
不。
No.
你杀了格雷格。
You killed Greg.
来保护你。
To protect you.
我不得不。
I had to.
你能诚实地回答这个问题吗?
Will you answer this honestly?
好的,我保证。它是什么?
Okay, I promise. What is it?
你是…
Did you...
与约旦吗?
With Jordan?
不。
No.
不,我没有……我没有。我永远不会。
No, I didn't... I didn't. I would never.
我爱你，好吗?
I love you, okay?
你爱我吗?
Do you love me?
我只是想摸摸你。
I just wanted to touch you.
你吓唬我。
You frighten me.
苏菲:蜜蜂!
Sophie: Bee!
蜜蜂!
Bee!
我们必须待在一起!
We have to stay together!
蜜蜂!
Bee!
蜜蜂吗?
Bee?
你在哪里?
Where are you?
我爱你。
I love you.
我们必须待在一起。
We have to stay together.
蜜蜂!
Bee!
——好的。——蜜蜂!
- Okay. - Bee!
嘿,嘿。
Hey, hey.
我一直在到处找你。
I've been looking for you everywhere.
我得告诉你一件事。
I have to tell you something.
我去爱丽丝的房间，然后我…
I went to Alice's room and I...
然后我发现了可卡因，然后…
And then I found coke and then...
我…我跟艾玛说了这么多，她…
I... I said all these things to Emma and she...
我…我给她吃药是因为…
I... I gave her pills 'cause...
然后她绊了一跤。
And then she tripped and fell.
这是我的错。
It's my fault.
索菲娅,没关系。没关系。
Sophie, it's okay. It's okay.
苏菲:我以为没人会相信我。
Sophie: I thought no one would believe me.
把手机给我。
Give me your phone.
什么?
What?
我想看看你和乔丹的短信。
I want to see your text with Jordan.
不。
No.
我得看看你的短信。
I have to see your texts.
好吗?
Please?
索菲娅:不。索菲娅。
Sophie: No. Sophie.
苏菲:停!
Sophie: Stop!
那不是我的手机。
That's not my phone.
哦……什么?
Oh... what?
那不是我的手机。
That's not my phone.
♬好吧，我在家里很无聊，我在家里很无聊
♪ Okay, I'm bored in the house and I'm in the house bored
♬在房子里无聊，我在房子里无聊
♪ bored in the house and I'm in the house bored
♬无聊在他妈的在房子无聊
♪ bored in the motherfuckin' in the house bored
♬我在他妈的无聊
♪ and I'm bored in the motherfuckin'
♬在房子里无聊
♪ in the house bored
♬在房子里无聊，在房子里无聊
♪ bored in the house, bored in the house bored
♬我在他妈的无聊
♪ I'm bored in the motherfuckin'
♬在房子里无聊
♪ in the house bored
♬我在他妈的无聊
♪ and I'm bored in the motherfuckin'
♬在家里无聊，是
♪ in the house bored, aye
♪我很无聊，我很无聊，我很无聊
♪ I'm bored, I'm bored, I'm bored
♪是啊，我需要我一个厚厚的小鸡
♪ Aye, I need me a thick chicks
♬坐在沙发上
♪ sittin' on a couch
♬我正在看我的Netflix
♪ and I'm going through my Netflix
♬在狗娘养的无聊，我什么都不做
♪ bored in the motherfucker, I ain't doin' shit
♪告诉她把车拉起来，让它像nesquik一样晃动
♪ tell her pull up, make it shake like nesquik
♬脖子结冰了，我们无处可去，贱人
♪ neck frozen, we're nowhere to go, bitch
♪告诉那个贱人冷得像冰箱门
♪ Tell the bitch chill like refrigerator doors
♬我们可以热一些拉面
♪ we can heat up some ramen
♪不能去商店
♪ can't go to the store
♬甚至不能去巡演一个黑鬼如此无聊♬
♪ can't even go on tour a nigga so bored ♪
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我有接待。
I have reception.